we've been asked
to add an additional key value pair
to our car hash hash
objects have a built-in element
assignment method that we can use
there's a little bit of syntactical
sugar here
we'll place the key
within the square brackets
and assign that key to our chosen value
so in this case let's reassign the value
associated with the key color
from blue to green
and we'll output our car hash and see if
that change is reflected
and it is
so how can we create a new key value
pair inside of our hash
we can use the same syntax
if the key that we pass in does not
already exist
in the hash then it will be created
so in this case we want to create an
additional key
in our car hash year
and assign it to 2003
let's output our car hash again and see
if we now have
four key value pairs
and we do
so this handy built-in element
assignment method
can reassign existing values or
create new key value pairs within your
hash